This upper body tubing exercise is called the shoulder front raise.
Take your tubing which should be about light to medium resistance, place it down on the floor and step one foot into the tubing.
And the tubing should be right underneath the arch of your foot.
Start off by simply raising one arm at a time.
As you're doing the shoulder raise, make sure that you just lift your arm right to shoulder height.
You don't want to go any higher.
We don't want any problems with those shoulder joints.
And exhale as you lift, inhale as you lower.
Now if you want to make it a little more challenging, go both arms at the same time.
Lift up and lower down.
Always make sure that you have your abdominal muscle engaged and that will protect your back.
We are going to have great looking shoulders out there as we put those tank tops on; getting ready for the beach that's for sure.
And that is the shoulder front raise exercise using the tubing.